Guide to the Samuel R. Delany Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- May 2017 acquisition, 200.17; (249 boxes) + 1 record album storage
  - Materials deposited circa 1999, 1947-1999; 51.75; (52 boxes)
    - Journals, 1974-1999
      - circa 1990s
        - Journals, circa 1992 April 7, circa 1992 May 18 (Box 63)
          Includes: essay on comic writers; meeting notes; personal entries; "The Rhetoric of Sex, The Discourse of Desire"; address on S&M; Catherine Schoen to Chancellor O'Brien (1992 May 14); 'They Fly at Ciron'; miscellany re: "Angelina's Pizzeria"; miscellaneous letters to and from SRD; reproductions of early paintings of SRD; photoprints of SRD, Dennis Rickett, Iva Hacker-Delany; notes on 'The Volcano Lover'; "Recollections of Sontag Interview"; miscellany re: Iva Hacker-Delany high school graduation.
        - Journals, circa 1992 June 26, circa 1992 August 13 (Box 63)
          Includes: personal entries; clippings on Gay Pride Day; class notes (?); reflex essay on Sontag; press release for 'They Fly at Ciron'; photoprints of SRD and Dennis Rickett; SRD to Allison Walsh (1992 August 16); review of 'Evil Companions', holograph and computerscript; 'Phallos!'; publicity for 'They Fly at Ciron'.
        - Journals, circa 1992 September 13, 1992 November (Box 63)
          Includes: meeting notes; class notes; personal entries; miscellany re: Ariane Mnouchkine; miscellaneous letters; 'Phallos!'; miscellaneous clippings; "Atlantis: Model 1924"; insert: autobiographical reflections, computerscript; Personnel Committee notes.
        - Journals, circa 1992 December 10, circa 1992 December 31 (Box 63)
          Includes: notes on Raimonda Modiano lecture; class notes; clippings on NYC storm; notes for 'Atlantis'; photoprint of SRD and Dennis Rickett; holiday cards; notes and essay on Hart Crane; personal entries; "Atlantis: Model 1924"; essay on Hart Crane; 'Phallos!' (?); notes on talk by Tom Keenan; miscellaneous letters, cards.
        - Journals, circa 1993 February 3, circa 1993 March 22 (Box 63)
          Includes: "K. Leslie Steiner Interviews SR Delany"; untitled poetry; miscellaneous letters and notes; "Statement for 'Unspeakable Practices' Conference" and related materials; personal entries; "Atlantis: Model 1924"; programs; essay on Hart Crane; notes on talk by Geoff Ely; letter to Erin McGraw; notes on talks by Glenn Most, Ed Glissons, Ekhab Hamal; programs for SRD speaking engagements.
        - Journals, circa 1993 May 2, circa 1993 July 7 (Box 63)
          Includes: personal entries; miscellany re: "Queer Sites" conference; photoprints of SRD, Dennis Rickett; 'Mad Man' (?); miscellany re: trip to Cape Cod; publicity for Wesleyan edition of 'Tales...'.
        - Journals, circa 1993 September 2, 1993 October 26 - 1994 January 10 (Box 63)
          Includes: personal entries; 'Mad Man' (?); notes on Dennis Rickett's family; notes on biographer's seminar; essay on Hart Crane; notes on being a gay writer; "Timothy Hasler Chronology"; introduction to 'Longer Views'; clippings, notes, brochures; notes on Edmund White's reading from 'Genet'; interview with Al Marr (?); untitled poetry; notes on George Mason University engagement; 'Mad Man'; notes on selected poems of Marilyn Hacker; Hasler chronology; photoprints of SRD and others.
        - Journals, circa 1994 January 10, circa 1994 March 22 (Box 63)
          Includes: personal entries; 'Mad Man'; eulogy for "Meredith Frummer" by Iva Hacker-Delany; miscellaneous letters to and from SRD; syllabus for "Intro to S-F"; notes on Cornel West talk; poem: "Rats"; brochures, broadsides, clippings, photoprint of SRD; intro to 'Hogg' reading; notes for essay on "performance and practice"; class notes; 'Phallos!'; 'Mad Man'; notes on China Mountain Zhang lecture; essay on Haraway.
        - Journals, circa 1994 May 22, circa 1994 August 2 (Box 63)
          Includes: personal entries; "The Work of Technology in the Age of Esthetic Reproduction"; miscellany re: Gay Pride Day; Readercon 7; untitled poems; poem: "The Soul Talks to the Self"; photoprints of Mason Baily; "Eddy"; "Counter/Pain"; introduction to Book and Blow Festival reading; notes on personal health; notes on SRD's father.
        - Journals, circa 1994 September 28, 1995 January 1 (Box 63)
          Includes: lists and group letter drafts re: bound galleys of 'Atlantis'; essay on art and science; notes for talk on autobiography; poem: "The Poets"; essay on video art; miscellaneous photoprints; personal entries; reviews of 'They Fly at Ciron' and 'Atlantis'; programs for 92nd St. "Y" poetry series; miscellany re: "Having Our Say"; photoprint of SRD.
        - Journals, 1995 March, 1995 April 21 (Box 63)
          Includes: personal entries; photoprints of SRD and family; funeral program and eulogy for Margaret Boyd Delany by SRD; reviews of 'Atlantis', 'Mad Man'; class notes; notes on women and cyberspace symposium; personnel committee minutes; essay featuring character Pall Durriken (?); photoprint of SRD; letters to SRD.
        - Journals, 1995 July, 1995 September 9 (Box 63)
          Includes: review of 'To Write Like a Woman' by Joanna Russ; personal entries; letter to Dave Samuelson; letters to SRD; poem: "Black Poem"; notes on 'Hogg'; introduction to reading of "Tale of Potters and Dragons"; essay on publishing industry; notes on Octavio Paz; miscellany re: speaking engagement at University of Idaho.
        - Journals, circa 1995 October 23, 1995 November (?) (Box 63)
          Includes: personal entries; untitled poem; notes on Mike Feder interview with Stanley Crouch; "Coming/Out"; letters to SRD.
        - Journals, circa 1995 December 26, 1996 February 12 - March 16 (Box 64)
          Includes: personal entries; 'Shoat Rumblin'; "Coming/Out" (?); "Internet and Short Story" syllabus; letter to "Carey", "Mrs. Bryan". Essay on children and pornography.
        - Journals, circa 1996 March 21 (Box 64)
          Includes: essay on children and pornography; personal entries; class notes.
        - Journals, 1996 June - August, circa 1996 August 19 (Box 64)
          Includes: personal entries; poetry by SRD; letter to John Wideman; 'Phallos!'; "Major Essays I Would Like to Write"; notes on Flaubert; essay on comics; "Politics of Paraliterature" (?); 'Times Sqaure Blue'; photoprint of SRD; story featuring character Neoptolomus; 'Phallos!' (?); "Poetry and Evil".
        - Journals, circa 1996 November 9, circa 1997 February 4 (Box 64)
          Includes: personal entries; 'Phallos!'; comments on work by Kelly Faughman; letter to Dianna Taylor; "The Queer Laws"; untitled poem; "Poem to the Distant City"; clippings on SRD; dream entries; notes for 'Times Square Blue'; class notes; "Thoughts on Starting Modest - Witness at Second Millennium"; letter from Sheldon Novick (1997 March 7).
        - Journals, circa 1997 March, circa 1997 June 16 (Box 64)
          Includes: personal entries; letter to Carl Rollyson; 'Phallos!'; essay on Harlan Ellison; class notes; 'Shoat Rumblin'; 'Time Square Blue' prologue (?); biographical studies of SRD written in third person; 'Shoat Rumblin' (?); letter to Erin McGraw.
        - Journals, circa 1997 August 19, circa 1997 September 17 (Box 64)
          Includes: essay on 'Heinrick von Ofterdingen'; notes for 'Fred' class; "Politics of Paraliterary Criticism"; "Response to Women in S-F"; 'Shoat Rumblin'; essay on Novalis; "Monolog"; personal entries; class notes for Michigan State course; corrections for 'Bread and Wine'; notes on residency at Atlantic Center for the Arts; notes on 'Beloved'.
        - Journals, circa 1997 November 6, circa 1997 December 5 (Box 64)
          Includes: 'Shoat Rumblin'; essay on 'Beloved'; 'Phallos!'; notes on 'Hogg'; personal entries; notes on distinction between "discourse" and "social practices"; photoprints of SRD; 'Times Square'; "The Owls"; corrections for 'Bread and Wine'.
        - Journals, circa 1998 February 10, circa 1998 March 14 (Box 64)
          Includes: 'Phallos!'; 'Times Square'; class notes; personal entries; "The Queer Problem of Race"; 'Shoat Rumblin'; letter to Bill Bamberger (?); 'Times Square' (?); "The Owls"; essay on gender and sexual freedom.
        - Journals, circa 1998 April 29, circa 1998 June 1 (Box 64)
          Includes: 'Shoat Rumblin'; personal entries; "The Owls"; notes on James Baldwin; note on Foucault and Derrida; letters to Erin McGraw, Tom Disch (?); essay on writing and the public; Lance Olsen interview; 'Times Square'.
        - Journals, circa 1998 July 6, circa 1998 August 13 (Box 64)
          Includes: personal entries; 'Times Square'; notes on Readercon 10; letter from Ken James (1998 July 6); letters to Eric McGraw, "Suzanne", Mattie Wakefield; 'Shoat Rumblin'; review of de Becker; 'Gift of Fear'; Lance Olsen interview; "The Owls"; letters to Eric Solstein, Erin McGraw; letter from Jeff Storer (1998 September 1).
        - Journals, circa 1998 October 8, circa 1998 November 11 (Box 64)
          Includes: personal entries; 'Shoat Rumblin'; 'Times Square'; letter to Ken James, "Earl" (1998 November 11); notes on experimental fiction; essay on 'The Preacher'; notes on comic books; letters to Ken James, Erin McGraw, Shu Lee, Mark Shechner, Jeffrey Tucker; 'Phallos!'; essay on Old Testament.
        - Journals, circa 1999 February - March, circa 1999 March 27 (Box 64)
          Includes: personal entries; class notes; 'Shoat Rumblin'; 'Phallos!'; untitled poem; notes on Mt. Holyoke Politics of Sex seminar; notes on Out/Write conference; poem: "Icarus"; review of Joanna Russ biography; funeral program for Sadie Delany; anecdote about "Freddy"; letter to Erin McGraw; essay on Joanna Russ; letter from Vince Czyz (1999 March 30); notes on Susan Glaspell, 'A Jury of Her Peers'; essay on Hart Crane; phone messages.
        - Journals, circa 1999 April 30, circa 1999 May 22, 1999 May 12-21 (Box 64)
          Includes: personal entries; lectures on Kafka, 'The Metamorphosis'; 'Shoat Rumblin'; letters to Eric Solstein, "David", "Alan", Kelly Salman; essay on Hart Crane; "Owls"; letter to Ken James.
        - Undated notebook A, undated notebook B, circa 1984 - 1985, undated (Box 64)
          Includes: letter to Larry (McCaffery?); P/F (?); "'Science Fiction' and 'Literature'"; story with characters Qrelon, Blaz, and Wrinn.
        - Undated notebook C, circa 1976 (Box 64)
          Includes: "What does 'Science Fiction' Mean to Me?"; "The Future of S-F"; letter to "Paul"; inserts for 'The Dispossessed'; letters to Iban Hassen, Michael McClintock, "Daniel"; essay on "the way readers use books".
    - Personal papers, 1947-1999
      - Financial records, 1972-1999
        - Bills, statements, receipts, 1972-1999 (Box 64)
          Contains: bills, statements, receipts.
        - Expenses ledger, 1981-1982 (Box 64)
          Contains: expenses ledger.
        - Freelance invoices, 1986-06-1988-05 (Box 64)
          Contains: freelance invoices from/for William Morrow Co. (1988 May 20 - 21), Arbor House (1986 June - August); payroll stubs; 'Mirror Shades' (?) front and back matter with editorial notations by SRD.
      - Calendars, datebooks, and address logs, 1986-1998
        - Address logs, undated (Box 64)
          Contains: 3 books, 1 list on loose-leaf.
        - Calendar and datebook, 1986-1989-08 (Box 65)
        - Datebooks, 1989 March, 1989 May - December, 1990, 1992 (Box 65)
        - Datebooks, 1993, 1994, 1995 (Box 65)
        - Datebooks, 1996, 1997, 1998 (Box 65)
      - Personal memorabilia, 1947-1984-08-12
        - Student materials, 1947-1960 (Box 65)
          Contains: Dalton School attendance reports (1951 - 1953); narrative report cards (1948 January - 1951 May); graduation certificate (1956 June); Gretchen Murray to Margaret Delany (1947); Jesse Jackson to SRD (circa 1958 September 12); Gertie Wintner to Margaret Delany (circa 1960 May 9); Arthur Levitt to SRD (1960 May 18); two scholastic writing award check stubs (1959 April 23); photocopies of 'Science Survey' article with no byline, typescript.
        - Frank Romeo, 1984-08-12- (Box 65)
          Contains: Frank Romeo to Bishop Howard Hubbard, typescript.
        - Margaret Delany college papers, 1960 October 3 - 1981 May 12, undated (Box 65)
          Contains: "Moses and Mohammed as Prophets and Leaders", typescript (1979 April 30); "The Psychology of Death -- Two Perspectives", typescript with holograph corrections (undated); "Gerontology -- A Study", typescripy with holograph corrections (undated); "No Exit: Freedom and Responsibility", typescript (1981 May 12); "American Issues", typescript with holograph corrections (1980 December 2); "The Praise of Folly: Flatter and Self-love -- Folly and Erasmus", 2 drafts, typescript with holograph corrections (1981 April 7); "Unions and Rioting", typescript with holograph corrections (1980 November 4); untitled on emergence of modern market society, typescript with holograph corrections (undated); Flora Ford to Mrs. Delany, photocopy of holograph letter (1960 October 3); life dossier for Fordham Univerisity and diploma (1980 May 15).
      - Materials relating to Iva Hacker-Delany, 1987 - 1991, 1880 (?) (Box 65)
        Contains: narrative report card (1988); 5 student papers, typescript, computerscript, and holograph (1989, 1991); Certificate of Merit (1987); 'Manual of the First Congregational Church', Amherst, Massachusetts, pamphlet (1880?).
      - Legal papers, 1983 June 13, undated (Box 65)
        Contains: contracts; papers relating to Daniel McLaughlin criminal court case; passport (1983 June 13).
      - Vitae and biographical profiles, undated (Box 65)
      - Miscellaneous, 1979-1993-04-12
        - Unknown artist: sketches of SRD and Gregory Freidin, 1993-04-12- (Box 57)
        - "Mind Control Chart", circa 1979 - 1980 (Box 57)
          Contains: poster with holograph notes.
    - Academic materials, undated
      - Committee agendas and minutes, undated (Box 65)
      - Political and professional activities, undated (Box 65)
      - Student papers, undated (Box 65)
      - Syllabi and course materials, undated (Box 65)
    - Printed material, 1959-05-1999
      - By SRD [arranged chronologically], 1959-05-1999
        - "The Grave Diggers", 1959-05- (Box 65)
          Contains: "The Grave Diggers", published in 'Literary Cavalcade'.
        - "Voice from the Gallery", 1959-10-16- (Box 65)
          Contains: "Voice from the Gallery", published in 'Science Survey'.
        - "Driftglass", 1967-06- (Box 65)
          Contains: "Driftglass", published in 'IF'.
        - "Corona", 1967-10- (Box 65)
          Contains: "Corona", published in 'Fantasy and Science Fiction'.
        - "Lines of Power", 1968-05- (Box 65)
          Contains: "Lines of Power", published in 'Fantasy and Science Fiction'.
        - "Cage of Brass", 1968-06- (Box 65)
          Contains: "Cage of Brass", published in 'IF'.
        - "House A-Fire", 1968-07- (Box 65)
          Contains: "House A-Fire", published in 'Amazing'.
        - "They Fly at Ciron", 1971-06- (Box 65)
          Contains: "They Fly at Ciron", published in 'Fantasy and Science Fiction'.
        - "Fangs of Fire", issue of 'Wonder Woman', 1972- (Box 65)
          Contains: "Fangs of Fire", issue of 'Wonder Woman'.
        - "The Profession of Science Fiction: VIII Shadows -- Part I", 1974-05- (Box 65)
          Contains: "The Profession of Science Fiction: VIII Shadows -- Part I", published in 'Foundation: The Review of Science Fiction'.
        - "When is a Paradox not a Paradox?", 1975-03- (Box 65)
          Contains: "When is a Paradox not a Paradox?", published in 'Foundation: The Review of Science Fiction'.
        - "The Tale of Gorgik", 1979 summer (Box 65)
          Contains: "The Tale of Gorgik", published in 'Asimov's SF Adventure Magazine'.
        - "Seven Moons' Light Casts Computer Shadows", 1980 summer (Box 65)
          Contains: "Seven Moons' Light Casts Computer Shadows", published in 'Epic Illustrated'.
        - "On Writing and S-F", 1983-01-19- (Box 65)
          Contains: "On Writing and S-F", published in 'Essay: A Fortnightly Publication'.
        - "Some Reflections on 'The Fall of the Towers'", 1983 spring (Box 65)
          Contains: "Some Reflections on 'The Fall of the Towers'", published in New Moon. Includes: transcription of two WisCon V panel discussions in which SRD participated.
        - "Two Translations by Samuel R. Delany", 1984 fall (Box 65)
          Contains: "Two Translations by Samuel R. Delany", published in 'Lock Haven University Forum'.
        - "An Interview with Samuel R. Delany", 1984- (Box 65)
          Contains: "An Interview with Samuel R. Delany", published in 'Xignals'.
        - Cover page for "Manifesto for Cyborgs" by Donna Haraway, 1985 summer (Box 65)
          Contains: cover page for "Manifesto for Cyborgs" by Donna Haraway.
        - "Forward to an Afterword", 1986- (Box 65)
          Contains; "Forward to an Afterword", published in 'Complete Nebula Award-Winning Fiction of SRD', photocopy.
        - "An Interview with Samuel Delany", 1986 summer/fall (Box 65)
          Contains: "An Interview with Samuel Delany", published in 'Cottonwood', with Lloyd Hemingway.
        - Book cover jacket copy for 'Countersolar!', 'Dreams of an Unseen Planet', and 'Mirrorshades'., 1986- (Box 65)
          Contains: book cover jacket copy for 'Countersolar!', 'Dreams of an Unseen Planet', and 'Mirrorshades'.
        - "Interview" with Takayuki Tatsume, 1986 fall (Box 65)
          Contains: "Interview" with Takayuki Tatsume, published in 'Diacritics'.
        - "Tale of Rumor and Desire", 1987- (Box 65)
          Contains: "Tale of Rumor and Desire", reprint from Callaloo with illustrations by Gregory Frux.
        - "Othello in Brooklyn", 1987- (Box 65)
          Contains: "Othello in Brooklyn" (review of Long Island University production).
        - "Of Sex, Objects, Signs, Systems, Sales, SF, and Other things", 1987-03- (Box 65)
          Contains: "Of Sex, Objects, Signs, Systems, Sales, SF, and Other things", published in 'Australian Science Fiction Review', photocopy.
        - "Pigs (or, at any rate, grunts) in Space", 1987 spring (Box 65)
          Contains: "Pigs (or, at any rate, grunts) in Space" (film review of 'Aliens'), published in 'Night Cry'.
        - "Among the Blobs", 1987-04-1987-05 (Box 65)
          Contains: "Among the Blobs", published in 'New Moon'; Jan Bagstad to SRD (1987 April 29).
        - "Paperback Publishing", 1987-05- (Box 65)
          Contains: "Paperback Publishing", published in 'Duprass #3'.
        - "An Interview with Samuel R. Delany", 1987 spring (Box 65)
          Contains: "An Interview with Samuel R. Delany", interview with Ken James, published in 'Visions'.
        - "The Semiology of Science", 1987-07- (Box 65)
          Contains: "The Semiology of Science", published in 'Science-Fiction Studies'.
        - "Among the Blobs", 1988- (Box 65)
          Contains: "Among the Blobs", published in 'Mississippi Review'.
        - "Down to Earth with Sci-Fi's Delany: A Conversation with SRD by Al Cunningham", 1988- (Box 65)
          Contains: "Down to Earth with Sci-Fi's Delany: A Conversation with SRD by Al Cunningham", published in 'Lambda Rising Book Report'.
        - 'Wagner/Artaud', 1988- (Box 65)
          Contains: 'Wagner/Artaud', published by Ansatz Press.
        - "Eye to Eye with Samuel R. Delany: Some 'Real' Matters...", 1988-03- (Box 65)
          Contains: "Eye to Eye with Samuel R. Delany: Some 'Real' Matters...", interview with Takayuki Tatsumi, published in Science Fiction Eye.
        - "Excerpts from an Interview with Samuel R. Delany" (with Susan Shaforzck), 1983-03-07- (Box 66)
          Contains: "Excerpts from an Interview with Samuel R. Delany" (with Susan Shaforzck), published in 'English Notes'.
        - "'Sides' for reading at 'Tracks'", 1988-04-06- (Box 66)
          Contains: "'Sides' for reading at 'Tracks'".
        - "Saved by the TV Crew", review of 'The Day of Creation' by Ballard., 1988-05-15- (Box 66)
          Contains: "Saved by the TV Crew" (review of 'The Day of Creation' by Ballard), published in 'NY Times Book Review'.
        - "The Motion of Light in Water", 1988-06- (Box 66)
          Contains: "The Motion of Light in Water", published in 'High Times'.
        - "On the Unspeakable", 1988-08- (Box 66)
          Contains: "On the Unspeakable", published in 'Everyday Life'.
        - "Flow My Tears..." Theater and Science Fiction, 1988-09- (Box 66)
          Contains: "Flow Mt Tears..." Theater and Science Fiction, published in 'NY Review of Science Fiction'.
        - Interview with Johan Schimansky, 'Intercon 89', 1989- (Box 66)
          Contains: Interview with Johan Schimansky, 'Intercon 89' (in Swedish). Includes: "Driftglass" excerpt.
        - "An Unpublished Excerpt from Samuel R. Delany's 'The Motion of Light and Water'", 1989-06- (Box 66)
          Contains: "An Unpublished Excerpt from Samuel R. Delany's 'The Motion of Light and Water'", published in 'SF Advance'.
        - "How Publishers Perceive Gay Writers: Gay Content in Context", 1990 March/April (Box 66)
          Contains: "How Publishers Perceive Gay Writers: Gay Content in Context", published in 'AWP Chronicle'.
        - "The Life of/ and Writing", 1990-10- (Box 66)
          Contains: "The Life of/ and Writing", published in 'NY Review of Science Fiction'.
        - "On 'Triton' and Other Matters: An Interview with Samuel R. Delany", 1990-11- (Box 66)
          Contains: "On 'Triton' and Other Matters: An Interview with Samuel R. Delany", published in 'Science-Fiction Studies'.
        - "An Antiphon", 1991-01- (Box 66)
          Contains: "An Antiphon", published in 'NY Review of Science Fiction'. Includes: photocopy of article and revised computerscript.
        - "Gay Sci Fi Meets Reality", interview with Will Doherty, 1989? (Box 66)
          Contains: "Gay Sci Fi Meets Reality", interview with Will Doherty.
        - "Twilight in the Rue Morgue", 1991- (Box 66)
          Contains: "Twilight in the Rue Morgue", published in 'Transition'.
        - "From Erik, Gwen, and D.H. Lawrence's Esthetic of Unrectified Feeling" and "An Interview with Samuel R. Delany" by Robert F. Reid-Pharr, 1991 spring (Box 66)
          Contains: "From Erik, Gwen, and D.H. Lawrence's Esthetic of Unrectified Feeling" and "An Interview with Samuel R. Delany" by Robert F. Reid-Pharr, published in 'Callaloo'.
        - "Citre et Trans", 1991 spring (Box 66)
          Contains: "Citre et Trans", published in Pacific Review.
        - "Introduction" to Miracleman, 1992- (Box 66)
          Contains: "Introduction" to Miracleman.
        - "Pornography/Censorship", 1992-04-1992-05 (Box 66)
          Contains: "Pornography/Censorship", published in 'American Book Review'.
        - "Underneath the Volcano with Susan Sontag", 1992- (Box 66)
          Contains: "Underneath the Volcano with Susan Sontag", published in 'Reflex', photocopy.
        - "Zelazny/Varley/Gibson -- and Quality (Part I)", 1992-08- (Box 66)
          Contains: "Zelazny/Varley/Gibson -- and Quality (Part I)", published in 'NY Review of Science Fiction'.
        - "The Future of the Body -- and Science Fiction and Technology", 1992-11- (Box 66)
          Contains: "The Future of the Body -- and Science Fiction and Technology", published in 'NY Review of Science Fiction'.
        - "Excerpt from 'The Splendor and Misery of Bodies, of Cities'", 1992-05-19- (Box 66)
          "Excerpt from 'The Splendor and Misery of Bodies, of Cities'", published in 'Reflex'. Includes: "Delany Considered as the Savior of Semi-Jaded Drones" by Elizabeth Hand.
        - "The Desert of Time", 1992-05- (Box 66)
          Contains: "The Desert of Time", published in 'Omni'.
        - "Tribute to Judith Merrill", 1993- (Box 66)